{
    "id": "6c4cf906cb0c463ba5c58947e41b2653",
    "title": "At, or or in",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2e67368c516245cb8b5eb588c1b6c5dd",
            "title": "At, Or, In",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I saw a beautiful girl ………………… the shop.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met her ………………. a party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a spelling mistake …………………. line nine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He works ………………….. the US.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Grandmother is arriving ………………… the 30 train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a student …………………. Cambridge.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is that pretty girl …………………. the second row?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cat is ………………. the piano.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why do you wear that ring ………………… your index finger?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Eat ………………. the Modern Restaurant. They serve the best food in town.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}